This is an example landing page done through the Odin Project. This is the course's first instance of having the student use both html and css to make a clone of an example landing page give. (See odin-landing-page/image/example.png for what was assigned). 

This project has the student use a myriad of css skills, primarily and most importantly formatting with flexbox. Ancillary skills such as the box-model, and font/styling and also required to complete this challenge.

To see the live version of my project visit: https://bradleysreynolds.github.io/odin-landing-page/
